https://www.talentsoft.com/privacy-policy

Language :
Contact
Language :
Privacy policy
TALENTSOFT, is a limited liability company with a share capital of 2,569,789 euros (€), registered at the Nanterre Trade and Companies Register under number 497 941 377, intra-Community VAT number FR87497941377, and registered office at 8 Rue Heyrault – 92100 Boulogne-Billancourt, France.
The company TALENTSOFT and its subsidiaries pay very close attention to guaranteeing respect for the rights and freedoms of users of the company’s website (hereinafter referred to as the “Website”).
TALENTSOFT undertakes to ensure all legal and regulatory provisions applicable to the protection of personal data are respected, and particularly EU Regulation 2016/679, of 27 April 2016 on the protection of natural persons with regard to processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data (hereinafter referred to as the “GDPR”) as well as the French Data Protection Act of 6 January 1978, as amended (hereinafter referred to as the “Act”).
This Privacy Policy describes the categories of data that TALENTSOFT collects from you, the reasons for collecting them, the way in which TALENTSOFT uses these data, as well as the rights you are entitled to.
Your personal data
1.1 What is personal data?
As defined by the French National Data Protection Authority (CNIL), the Act, and the GDPR, personal data  means any information relating to an identified or identifiable natural person (‘data subject’); an identifiable natural person is one who can be identified, directly or indirectly, in particular by reference to an identifier such as a name, an identification number, location data, an online identifier or to one or more factors specific to the physical, physiological, genetic, mental, economic, cultural or social identity of that natural person.
1.2 Controller
TALENTSOFT is the controller with regard to your personal data.
TALENTSOFT may be contacted through the following means:
– Postal address: TALENTSOFT, 8 Rue Heyrault, 92100 Boulogne-Billancourt – France;
– Email address: contact-ts@talentsoft.com.
Our Data Protection Officer is Mrs Julia WATKINS, who can be contacted with the following email address: jwatkins@talentsoft.com.
1.3 Categories of Data you share with TALENTSOFT
On a general basis, you can access the Website without having to provide any personal data. TALENTSOFT does not process data that allows it to identify you as a person, directly or indirectly, unless you have willingly provided this information by filling in the various forms that are provided to you or made available on the Website.
On the Website, elements of personal data that TALENTSOFT may request are your first and last names, telephone number, email address, current position, name of the company or companies you belong to, country, (hereinafter referred to as “Data”).
All Data that must be provided in order to access a particular service are indicated by an asterisk. Communicating your Data is voluntary, but if you choose not to communicate the information indicated by an asterisk, you will be unable to benefit from the services in question, including information, communication, or recruiting requests.
Data shall be processed using computer technology and stored in databases located exclusively within the European Union.
By communicating your Data, you authorise TALENTSOFT to process these Data for the purposes and duration described in this document. You may, at any time, withdraw your consent for the processing of your Data, in which case TALENTSOFT will cease the related processing activities.
When you communicate your Data, you provide us with a guarantee that you have received the authorisations and consent required from the individuals concerned by these Data if the Data concerns people other than yourself and, if applicable, for the purposes described in this document.
Your Data are not subject to automated decision-making, including profiling.
TALENTSOFT neither collects nor seeks out, intentionally, sensitive personal data or data concerning individuals under 13 years of age. Children under the age of 13 are not allowed to use the Website on their own. Should we learn that despite our efforts, such personal data for a child under 13 have been collected without parental consent, we will, without undue delay, delete all this information and all backups that may have been made.
When you visit the Website, TALENTSOFT uses cookies to identify your IP address and browser in order to draw up statistics on indicators such as Website traffic, page views, and language preferences.
Your IP address is immediately anonymised after use. Therefore, TALENTSOFT cannot, in any case, identify you through this means. For more information, please refer to our Cookies Policy.
1.4 Recipient of your Data
TALENTSOFT may share your Data with other entities within the TALENTSOFT group, for the sole purposes provided in Article 1.6 of this Privacy Policy and under the strict conditions set out in this Privacy Policy.
TALENTSOFT may send your Data to its partner, the company MARKETO, in order to process your data for the purposes listed in the article 1.5. For further information, please refer to our Cookies Policy.
Besides the recipient listed in this article, your Data are not communicated nor transferred to any other third party.
All the recipients of your Data are required to respect data confidentiality and to process your data for the purposes listed in the article 1.5, under the direct control of TALENTSOFT.
However, TALENTSOFT may be obliged, under the Act and/or the GDPR, or under any other applicable legal provision, to communicate your Data following a court ruling, order, decree, or any other applicable legal provision and/or regulation.
1.5 Purpose for processing your Data
By communicating your Data, TALENTSOFT processes your Data for one or several of the following purposes:
Communication:
We will respond to your comments and to any other requests you may address us, including online questions. In sending us a form and agreeing to receive our communications, you allow TALENTSOFT to contact you by telephone and/or by email.
For this purpose, we shall process your Data for the duration of our exchanges and for a maximum of twenty-four (24) months from the last time you contacted us (by email, phone call, ect.). After this date, your Data shall be erased, unless you ask us to keep it.
Information
We may, on the basis of the information contained in the forms you send us, send you information and specific content on TALENTSOFT offers and on TALENTSOFT events.
For this purpose, we shall process your Data for the duration of our exchanges and for a maximum of twenty-four (24) months from the last time you contacted us (by email, phone call, ect.). After this date, your Data shall be erased, unless you ask us to keep it.
Recruitment
If you share your online CV or any other form of application with us, we will use your Data for recruiting purposes. We may contact you by email, telephone, or postal address. Additional information on the manner in which your Data are used by TALENTSOFT during the recruiting process will be shared with you as the process moves on.
For this purpose, we shall process your Data for the duration of our exchanges and for a maximum of twenty-four (24) months from the last time you contacted us (by email, phone call, ect.). After this date, you shall be contacted and asked if you want to update your Data. Without an answer within one (1) month, your Data shall be erased from our databases.
1.6 Legal basis for processing
Your Consent: We process your Data only if you have given consent to this processing for the purposes listed hereabove. AT ANY TIME, YOU MAY WITHDRAW YOUR CONSENT FOR PROCESSING YOUR DATA. In this case, processing will cease and the Data in question will be erased without undue delay. Withdrawal of your consent does not compromise the lawfulness of the processing, based on consent, carried out prior to consent withdrawal.
Our legitimate interest: In accordance with article 6, paragraph 1, point (f) of the GDPR, TALENTSOFT has a legitimate interest in sharing your Data with the entities listed in article 1.4, to process your Data for the purposes listed above in the best possible way.
1.8 Your rights
As part of the processing of your Data and in accordance with the Act and the GDPR, you have the following rights:
Right to access (Article 15 of the GDPR);
Right to rectification (Article 16 of the GDPR);
Right to erasure (Article 17 of the GDPR);
Right to restriction of processing (Article 18 of the GDPR);
Right to data portability (Article 20 of the GDPR);
Right to object (Article 21 of the GDPR).
The rights listed above are personal and may only be exercised by people who have communicated their Data to TALENTSOFT.
To exercise your rights or to submit any other request about the processing of your Data, you can contact TALENTSOFT by contacting the Webmaster using the contact form on the portal (go to the “Contact” tab and submit your request using the message area).
When you contact TALENTSOFT directly, through whichever means, TALENTSOFT reserves the right to keep a record of this correspondence for a period necessary for processing the request.
You also have the right to lodge a complaint with the data protection authority. In France, the data supervisory authority is the CNIL (3 Place de Fontenoy, TSA 80715 – 75334 PARIS CEDEX 07).
Cookies
The Website uses cookies. A description of cookies and similar technology used on the Website can be found in the Website’s Cookies Policy.
Responsibility
TALENTSOFT’s responsibility in the application of this Privacy Policy cannot exceed the limits established in the General Conditions of Use (GCU).
Miscellaneous
TALENTSOFT reserves the right to amend or update its Privacy Policy at any time. As such, you are invited to consult this page regularly, since any browsing within the Website means you agree to the most recent version of the Privacy Policy.
A warning will be published and displayed on the Website when any significant amendment is made to this Privacy Policy.
This Privacy Policy was initially drawn up in French. Should there be any differences or contradictions with a version in a different language, the French version alone will be considered as authoritative and will apply.
